易考范文十四
Obviously, the picture above depicts an exciting event,
a milestone in our country's space exploration:
the first lunar probe of China was launched.
Named after a Chinese goddess who flew to the moon,
Chang'e No.1 spreads its wings in the outer space,
fulfilling the dream of flying to the moon,
which Chinese people have cherished for thousands of years.
China has witnessed a giant leap in the outer space research in recent years.
These achievements will undoubtedly benefit Chinese people,
even humanity as a whole.
To begin with, the successful launch of satellites
and manned spacecraft builds our confidence
in making more headway in the space exploration.
Besides, the analysis and exploitation of the useful materials
beneath the lunar surface will make it possible
to supplement the natural resources of the globe,
which are on the verge of being exhausted.
However, many people are not supportive of space research.
The enormous amount of money and energy wasted on the project,
they argue, might have been devoted to those struggling for food and shelter.
What's more, they are troubled by the idea that
excessive space exploitation will eventually lead to catastrophe of the world.
Therefore, they suggest the pace should be slowed down.
Despite those doubts and hesitations,
the advantages of the space research far outweigh its disadvantages.
It will certainly usher in a brighter world for us.